<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Hexo</title>
  <subtitle>Composing Flows, Spreading Memes</subtitle>
  <link href="/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://temp.sunebear.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-04-23T06:54:13.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://temp.sunebear.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>SuneBear</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="http://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Why I decided to stop writing</title>
    <link href="http://temp.sunebear.com/2016/paused/"/>
    <id>http://temp.sunebear.com/2016/paused/</id>
    <published>2016-04-22T09:07:05.000Z</published>
    <updated>2016-04-23T06:54:13.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Hey everybody,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That sounds terrible to me? Actually, I don’t think so. Of course, I know writing is very important to expressing thoughts and life, especially for newbie writers have an occasional day off.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past two years, I posted off and on &lt;a href=&quot;/2015&quot;&gt;dozens of articles&lt;/a&gt;. Since October 8, 2015, the day after National Day—I’ve stopped writing the blog. There are so many reasons to explain why I do it. However, these are too subjective to talk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a few words, I am just not enjoy writing anymore, even when I created a minimalist theme &lt;code&gt;dandelion&lt;/code&gt; with elegant typography. There are philosophical questions below I’ve asked myself for months:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Why did I write it down? For sharing stories or relieving pressure?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What’s my writing worth?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How much do I know about myself?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, now I got an answer that keeping the writing paused for a long period of time in public platforms. I will spend more time in composing fantastic flows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep silent and compose flows for a better new beginning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kindly,&lt;br&gt;SuneBear&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    
    <summary type="html">
    
      &lt;p&gt;Hey everybody,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That sounds terrible to me? Actually, I don’t think so. Of course, I know writing is very important to expressing t
    
    </summary>
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
